<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: singularity | tuvokki.github.com]]></title>
  <link href="http://tuvokki.github.com/blog/categories/singularity/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://tuvokki.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-18T21:34:24+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://tuvokki.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Wouter Roosendaal]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restructuring, focus and vision]]></title>
    <link href="http://tuvokki.github.com/blog/2012/11/18/Restructuring-focus-and-vision/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-18T18:10:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://tuvokki.github.com/blog/2012/11/18/Restructuring-focus-and-vision</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4>Big words</h4>

<p>Lack of structure, focus and vision are the key values of this this blog. And that lack of direction is also the recurring theme is this symphony of scattered efforts. Maybe time to do something about it.</p>

<h4>Proposal</h4>

<p>Allthough I am married to JAVA, my secret misstress is python. And for a mistress she's nce. She's got Django. And apart from loving python, I love its modularity. So why am I distributing complete installations like the fnurkels and the picture project. So I will get all thos monolithic installs from the list and I will distribute them as they are bound to be: in Django apps.</p>

<h4>Future</h4>

<p>And that is all in the future. For me it rhymes with structure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[where to go from here]]></title>
    <link href="http://tuvokki.github.com/blog/2012/10/30/Where-to-go-from-here/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-30T09:59:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://tuvokki.github.com/blog/2012/10/30/Where-to-go-from-here</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4>Nothing's new</h4>

<p>I always thought that reudcing the number of blogs I 'maintained' would result in better and more quality blogposts in the remaining few. Now I know that is not true.</p>

<p>The average amount of inspiration is not rising when fewer posts are written. It stays roughly the same.</p>

<h4>Poor quality</h4>

<p>The number of poor quality-posts has no influence on the average quality.</p>

<p>Ah well, whatever. There is still no vision or idea behind this blog. There is no clue where to go from here. Nobody knows. And frankly, I really don't think anobody cares. Maybe I should, but I see no reason why.</p>

<p>Nothing has changed since the last time I wrote a blog here. 'till next time.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
