<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: structure | tuvokki.github.com]]></title>
  <link href="http://tuvokki.github.com/blog/categories/structure/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://tuvokki.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-19T20:59:04+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://tuvokki.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Wouter Roosendaal]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rare event]]></title>
    <link href="http://tuvokki.github.com/blog/2012/11/19/Rare_event/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-19T20:45:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://tuvokki.github.com/blog/2012/11/19/Rare_event</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4>there has neven been ..</h4>

<p>It is not uncommon that I predict change. Or that I announce it, even. But it is very rare that I follow up on such a lifechanging decision. Right now (look at the dates of this post and the previous), a rare event has happened. The result can be found here:</p>

<p><a href="https://github.com/tuvokki/about">about</a> *A simple implementation of an about section for a Django website</p>

<p>I really did something with my last post.</p>

<p><img src="http://logo-city.org/data_images/4260/E76/40438.png" alt="image" /></p>

<p>That's great!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restructuring, focus and vision]]></title>
    <link href="http://tuvokki.github.com/blog/2012/11/18/Restructuring-focus-and-vision/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-18T18:10:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://tuvokki.github.com/blog/2012/11/18/Restructuring-focus-and-vision</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4>Big words</h4>

<p>Lack of structure, focus and vision are the key values of this this blog. And that lack of direction is also the recurring theme is this symphony of scattered efforts. Maybe time to do something about it.</p>

<h4>Proposal</h4>

<p>Allthough I am married to JAVA, my secret misstress is python. And for a mistress she's nce. She's got Django. And apart from loving python, I love its modularity. So why am I distributing complete installations like the fnurkels and the picture project. So I will get all thos monolithic installs from the list and I will distribute them as they are bound to be: in Django apps.</p>

<h4>Future</h4>

<p>And that is all in the future. For me it rhymes with structure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
